EUGENE GARRETT

Full Stack Developer

@ eugenegarrett.dev0614@gmail.com

O Houston, TX, United State

SUMMARY

I have been working as a full stack developer for 8 years now. My main skills are React, Next.js, Node.js, Java and I have gained great experience in software development. I have gained a reputation as a trusted advisor and a valuable asset to any organization due to my ability to identify growth opportunities and tackle complex challenges. I can say that I am a creative, calm, detail-oriented person who loves to learn from others. My hobbies include soccer and occasionally playing computer games with friends. I am actively looking for a new job as a full stack developer and am ready to work for you immediately! Thank you.

EDUCATION

04/2012 - 08/2016

Bachelor of Computer Science
Technological Institute of the Philippines

EXPERIENCE

10/2021 - 05/2024 •

Senior Full Stack Developer

Venngage

- · In particular, I have completed a number of front-end projects using Next.js and implemented unit tests using various testing frameworks.
- · I gained practical experience in teamwork and Agile & Scrum methodologies with great team members.
- · We have satisfied many potential customers by building responsible and high-quality projects and have always received good reviews.

05/2018 - 10/2021

Senior Full Stack Developer

Worka

- · Proactively liaised with the designers and project manager to ensure efficient and timely delivery of significant projects.
- · Built several NFT marketplaces with LazyMint, Auction, and fixed price sell/buy features using React.js and Solidity languages.

11/2016 - 04/2018

Junior Web Developer

EACOMM

- Trained 1 year with 5 junior web developers from one of the senior team members about frontend development.
- · Design and establish user-friendly websites, including optimized check-out page, resulting in a 30% increase in user clicks and purchases.
- · Establish an interactive and dynamic website that guarantee high traffic, page views, and maximum user experience.

SKILLS

HTML / CS	S / JavaSri _l	ot SCSS	SCSS / Bootstrap / Tailwind CSS / MUI				ipt 2015+	TypeScript	
React.js	Redux	Next.js	Node.js	Express.js	Java	MySQL	GraphQL	MongoDB	C++
Algorithm	Solidit	y hardh	nat truffl	e ERC20/	ERC721 /	'ERC1155	Git Gr	eat Team Work	